<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data science portfolio on Jose Hernandez</title>
    <link>https://hernandezjose0.github.io/Data_Science_Portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data science portfolio on Jose Hernandez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 11:00:59 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hernandezjose0.github.io/Data_Science_Portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Shared bikes predictor</title>
      <link>https://hernandezjose0.github.io/Data_Science_Portfolio/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hernandezjose0.github.io/Data_Science_Portfolio/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Rented bikes is a service who has gained popularity recently. While a sunny and fresh day can be the best scenario to go and take a ride, weather is a tricky factor, rain and snow are impediments to rent bikes. So, in order to make sure we can supply enough bikes per country we need to find a way to predict the demand. Let&amp;rsquo;s ride through data and discover a solution!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space X rocket landing predictor</title>
      <link>https://hernandezjose0.github.io/Data_Science_Portfolio/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hernandezjose0.github.io/Data_Science_Portfolio/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>The Space X company offers their service of special missions and have rockets with a cost of 62 million dollars, they save a lot of money because the rocket’s first stage is reusable if landing successfully, since the most popular model is Falcon 9, we’re going to focus on this rocket model. The Space X webpage contain many features of all the space mission made up until today that can help us in order to predict if the first stage will land successfully and save a lot of money to the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://hernandezjose0.github.io/Data_Science_Portfolio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hernandezjose0.github.io/Data_Science_Portfolio/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Jose Hernandez I&amp;rsquo;m an student of Computer sciences at IPN. I&amp;rsquo;m an enthusiast of data science and machine learning, I like to understand the story that data want to tell through statistics and maths, and share it to people who can use it to take decisions and improve business. Collecting, cleaning, visualizing data and developpe machine learning models are the tools I use to understand data and improve the insights I get from it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://hernandezjose0.github.io/Data_Science_Portfolio/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hernandezjose0.github.io/Data_Science_Portfolio/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can follow me here:
Site URL Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jose-guadalupe-hernandez-hernandez-3871271bb/ GitHub: https://github.com/HernandezJose0 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
